

PROFILE

Austin Coding Academy graduate with one year of working experience on an in-house built enterprise level e-commerce platform & CMS. Along with various other past experiences which help me in being a dynamic and understanding teammate! I am in search of an opportunity where I can apply my diverse background and skills to benefit a collaborative and inclusive team.

EDUCATION

Austin Coding Academy – September, 2018 - August, 2019: Full Stack JavaScript Kilgore College — May, 2013: Associates of Arts

SKILLS/TECHNOLOGIES

Git, NodeJS, ES6, Javascript, CSS/SASS, React, Redux, AngularJS, Bootstrap, MongoDB, SQL, SqlServerManagementService (SSMS), VSCode, Visual Studio, Postman, IIS, Azure, CMS: DotNetNuke(DNN), Scrum Implementation.

EXPERIENCE

COMMUNITY MODERATOR, BIGCOMMERCE - NOVEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

JR FRONT END ENGINEER, CLARITY VENTURES — DECEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

- Daily: Workflows through Azure sprints, utilizing scrum practices, logging time to bill clients, completing FE tickets & communicating with fellow devs, PMs, and management.

Accomplishments:

- Leading by example in content creation for new & current employees by uploading company stack overflow questions & answers, as well as creating internal documentation, training videos & teams wiki updates.
- Completing front end tickets on/ahead of time and being known as the most communicative developer within my team to our PMs on concerns, needs, successes and requirements/possible risks on change requests, especially when nee.
- Started communications and actionable items within my company on internal pain points, and being a voice for my teammates. Being a key member in the action of adopting a recognition program into the company, to help nurture the company culture.
- Always providing impactful feedback in sprint retros and within communications
- Company Stack: AngularJS, C#. Product: In-house E-commerce software & CMS(DNN).

SERVER, RAZZOOS — OCTOBER 2018 - NOVEMBER 2019

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE (CSR), VISA - FEBRUARY 2018 - OCTOBER 2018

Moving on from the sales world, I found an opportunity with Visa providing fraud prevention services and third-party card services for financial institutions all over the US & Canada. Became inspired to go back to school by our amazing VP of the department.

SALES REPRESENTATIVE, YODLE - WEB.COM — DECEMBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2017

My first position in the tech-world! Phone sales: cold calling, setting demo appointments, running and closing demos. My commitment to ethical sales kept my success high and my churn-rate extremely low. Sales lab leader for a new <u>web.com</u> product, after acquisition.

COMMUNITY

Rocket.Build Hackathon — May, 2019 : Participant Youth Code Jam — February, 2019 : Volunteer